#### 

EN

### iMazing Values Your Privacy

We use cookies to enhance this website experience, serve personalized ads or content and analyze our traffic. By clicking 'Consent' you accept the use of cookies.

For more information, please refer to our [Cookie policy](https://imazing.com/privacy-policy)

### Manage your Cookie Preferences

**Essential cookies** are essential for basic website functionality or serve a legitimate business purpose.  
These cookies can be disabled by changing your browser preferences.

**Analytical cookies** help us to improve our website by collecting and reporting information on its usage.

**Marketing cookies** help us to monitor campaigns and improve the relevancy of campaigns you receive.

For more information, please refer to our [Cookie policy](https://imazing.com/privacy-policy)

Manage Consent

Accept Selection Accept All

*  Personal
    
    Features

    Products

*  Business

    Products

    Solutions

    Learn More

*  Company

*  Support

EN

* EN

Privacy Policy
==============

**_Contents_**  

1. [Commitment and general principles](#commitment)
2. [Purposes of data processing](#purposes)  
    
3. [User management and right to information](#right)  
    
4. [Nondisclosure of information](#nondisclosure)  
    
5. [Safety & confidentiality](#safety)  
    
6. [Cookie policy](#cookie-policy)  
    
7. [Newsletter policy](#newsletter)  
    
8. [Customer Experience Program and crash reporting](#customer-experience)
9. [Collected data by service](#partners)  
    
10. [Links to third-party websites](#links)  
    
11. [Updates to this privacy policy](#update)  
    
12. [Contact](#contact)  

1\. Commitment and general principles
-------------------------------------

We ([DigiDNA LLC](https://www.zefix.ch/en/search/entity/list/firm/916184?name=digidna&searchType=exact), hereafter DigiDNA) commit to comply with Switzerland's [New Federal Act on Data Protection (nFADP)](https://www.kmu.admin.ch/kmu/en/home/facts-and-trends/digitization/data-protection/new-federal-act-on-data-protection-nfadp.html), as well as [European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/reg/2016/679/oj). Regardless of the laws applicable to you, we are firmly committed to upholding the highest standards and principles of data protection and privacy.

**Our apps are built to empower our users by giving them broad access to their own data. We do not access, nor have access to, any user data handled by our apps: files are stored on our users' own devices, none of these files nor their contents are ever uploaded to our servers, saved, retained or shared with us or any third party.  
[Learn more about our software's security and privacy features.](https://imazing.com/security-and-privacy)**

We collect only personal data that is adequate, relevant, and limited to what is necessary for providing the best customer service. Moreover, we do not store or process any personal data ourselves. Instead, we rely on third-party services with strong ethics and privacy standards to provide our services in a way that respects our users' data and privacy (see below: [Collected data by service](#partners)).

The personal data that we do have access to is necessary for us to provide efficient customer support, license management, dispute handling (refunds), as well as timely information about the purchased product. Such data includes name, email address, type and date of purchase, license type and activation related data, as well as communications with our support team. **At no point does DigiDNA has access nor can store any sensitive payment information such as credit card number or PayPal account details.**

Our staff works in compliance with the strictest standards of care and confidentiality. Processing of your personal data is carried out in full accordance with the applicable regulations.

2\. Purposes of data processing
-------------------------------

We only collect personal data for our customer service. This includes and is limited to purchases of licenses, support tickets, and newsletter subscriptions.

For your needs as an individual customer, your email address is collected for your license management, informations on updates of the product you purchased, potential security issue warnings, and support request follow-ups.

For the needs of all current and prospective customers, we may use your data in a fully anonymized manner for product development prospects, internal statistics relevant to the satisfaction of our customers (such as general trends or preferences) or general improvements of our products and services or other business-relevant data traffic information. (Please refer to [Cookie policy](#cookie-policy) and [Collected data by service](#partners) for more information.)

3\. User management and right to information
--------------------------------------------

You may request access to your personal data at any time to view, update, or delete it. To do so, please send your request electronically via [our secure contact form](https://imazing.com/contact), or by postal mail at **DigiDNA, Boulevard des Tranchées 4, 1205 Geneva, Switzerland.**

4\. Nondisclosure of information
--------------------------------

Unless required by law or legal injunctions, we only share personal data with the partners listed in the [Collected data by service](#partners) section below and for the purposes outlined in the [Purposes of data processing](#purposes) section above.

5\. Safety & confidentiality
----------------------------

All communications between your web browser and our website, as well as between our software products and our servers, are secured by industry-standard SSL encryption.

Furthermore, access to your personal data is restricted to employees directly involved in customer support and analytics—who have been trained to observe our strict standards of care and confidentiality.

Nevertheless, it must be noted that the Internet is by nature not a completely secure space for any data; you duly understand and agree that DigiDNA is not responsible for any direct or indirect damages resulting from events such as, but not limited to, malicious third-party actions or technical failures of any nature.

6\. Cookie policy
-----------------

DigiDNA uses cookies to enhance its service as well as to analyze its websites' usage. DigiDNA is committed to respecting your privacy and informing you transparently about the ways in which it collects your data.

### Cookies set by DigiDNA

We set the following persistent cookies:

2. **Essential Cookies**  
    
    They are essential for basic website functionality or serve a legitimate business purpose. These cookies can be disabled by changing your browser preferences.  
    
    **\_\_ddna\_\_analytics\_consent** and **\_\_ddna\_\_marketing\_consent** store the visitor's consent settings for analytics and marketing cookies, respectively.  
    **\_\_ddna\_\_campaign** and **\_\_ddna\_\_source** contain utm parameters which inform us about how users reached our website.  
    **\_\_ddna\_\_coupon** stores a coupon code you entered or which carried over from a link in order to apply a discount upon checkout.  
    
    We also set anonymized cookies from our partner **Impact** to reward our affiliates. You can learn about it here:

3. **Analytical cookies**  
    
    They help us to improve our website by collecting and reporting information on its usage.
    
    We rely on **Google Analytics** and use the collected anonymized data to analyze website usage and improve our content and user experience accordingly. You can learn more here:

4. **Marketing cookies**  
    
    We advertise with Google Ads and in order to track our marketing and advertising efforts we rely on cookies set by Google. You can learn more about their policy and opt out using the links below:

### Managing cookies

You can review and edit your consent settings for the analytical and marketing cookies set by DigiDNA at all times using the following link: [Manage cookies](javascript:void(0)).

Regarding our own essential cookies, our partners' cookies, and any other third-party cookies, all modern internet browsers provide you with complete control over them. Browser settings allow you to block and delete cookies. Here's a non-exhaustive collection of useful links:

To learn more about your ability to manage cookies, refer to the privacy features in your preferred browser.

7\. Newsletter policy
---------------------

When you acquire a license for one of our products, you are automatically subscribed to our mailing list. This enables us to keep you updated on crucial improvements to the product you've purchased. Because we operate in Apple's ever shifting environment it is important for us to communicate with our users about security updates, new features and changes implied by iOS, iPadOS, tvOS, visionOS, iTunes, macOS or Windows updates. We might also inform you about other product updates, promotions or company news, but we tend to keep it to the essential—we won't swamp your inbox.

Additionally, we offer an optional opt-in subscription to our DigiDNA Deals newsletter: deals and offers on our own products or on products we hand-pick for their quality.

**We never, EVER share your email for third-party marketing purposes. That would be silly, and illegal.**

You can of course unsubscribe from any of our mailing lists at any time: every email we send contains an _Unsubscribe_ button, or using the link below. You can also review our email platform and sending partner **Mailchimp**'s privacy policy in the article dedicated to third-party providers below [Collected data by service](#mailing).

8\. Customer Experience Program and crash reporting
---------------------------------------------------

If you have opted in to participate in our **Customer Experience Program**, you've agreed to share anonymous usage statistics about how you interact with our software. You can opt out of this program at any time by toggling off the following setting in iMazing's main menu:  
_Preferences > General > Participate in the Customer Experience Program_

In the rare event of an app crash, submitting your crash report implies consent to share anonymized functional crash data.

In both scenarios mentioned, we never transmit personal data. For more information about the nature of these reports, please refer to [Crash reporting and app analytics](#microsoft-app-center).

9\. Collected data by service
-----------------------------

We work together with specialised partners for specific aspects of our services, such as payment processing, license management, customer support, and mailing list management. If for any reason you wish to access all or part of your data stored by these third parties, you can contact them directly, or [contact us](https://imazing.com/contact) and we'll be glad to assist you. You have the right to request a copy of your data, as well as to have it updated, deleted or transferred.

**Our products do not upload any personal data to ourselves or any third parties. The data we collect and store is strictly limited to information relevant to our services, such as your email address, purchase history of DigiDNA products, license code and activation status, and communications with our support team.**

1. **Payment Platforms**
    
    Order processing is handled by our online resellers and Merchants of Record, **Paddle.com** and **FastSpring.com**. These partners also manage order-related inquiries and returns.
    
    You can identify which platform was used for your specific payment by looking at your order number: if it starts with _DDNA_, the transaction was handled by FastSpring, otherwise by Paddle.
    
    #### Collected data
    
    Information provided by the user during the purchase process and data related to fraud prevention.
    
    **At no point does anyone at DigiDNA have access to sensitive payment information such as credit card number or PayPal account details.**
    
2. **License management, iMazing 2.13 and above**
    
    Starting from October 13th 2020 DigiDNA manages and validates licensing data. Said data is stored encrypted on **Google Cloud Platform** in the US. Collected data serves the following purposes:
    
    * License validation
    * Customer support (refunds, license extensions, computer and/or mobile identification to manage licenses, etc...)
    * Billing
    
    #### Collected data
    
    e-mail, name if given, license activation and order history, Paddle checkout ID and Subscription ID, computer and mobile device OS and model, unique anonymous device identifiers.
    
3. **Deprecated license management, before iMazing 2.13**
    
    **DevMate** handles license management (activation/deactivation) and crash reporting.
    
    #### Collected data
    
    e-mail, name if submitted when purchasing, license activation history.
    
    _**DevMate** platform has been retired on the 1st of November 2020, date after which DevMate servers have not stored any new user data and is only used to validate previously issued licenses on iMazing versions up to 2.13 (not inclusive)._
    
4. **iMazing Account**
    
    All data stored is encrypted on **Google Cloud Platform** in the US. Authentication is managed by **Auth0** and related user data is stored in the US. Collected data serves the following purposes:
    
    * User authentication
    * License management
    * Task delegation
    
    #### Collected data
    
    e-mail, name if given, computer and mobile device OS and model, unique anonymous device identifiers.
    
5. **Customer support**
    
    **ZenDesk** is our customer support platform of choice.
    
    #### Collected data
    
    support conversations history, data about the user's computer and product version as inputted by the user via the Contact form.

    **SupportYourApp** helps us with the technical support we provide to our users.
    
    #### Shared data
    
    selected trained agents have limited access to our **ZenDesk** account, as well as to relevant purchase and licensing data.
    
7. **Mailing**
    
    **Mailchimp** is our mailing list platform of choice.
    
    #### Shared data
    
    e-mail, name if submitted when purchasing, purchased product name and version, operating system (Windows or macOS), and marketing data such as campaign, source, coupon code and license type if applicable.
    
8. **Crash reporting and app analytics**
    
    We use **Microsoft App Center** to handle crash reporting and perform analytics in our apps.
    
    #### Collected data
    
    If a crash report is submitted, we collect crash details. We also gather environment data (OS version and system status). When users opt into our [**Customer Experience Program**](#customer-experience), we record in-app navigation events (without any user data). All this information is strictly associated with an anonymous user ID only.

10\. Links to third-party websites
----------------------------------

Our websites and software products may contain hypertext links towards other websites unrelated to DigiDNA. While we do our best to link to high quality resources, we shall neither be held responsible for the content of such websites, nor for data protection practices of third parties which operate them. We urge you to check and understand their privacy policies before providing them with your personal data.

11\. Updates to this privacy policy
-----------------------------------

* **2024/09/05:** updated information about _Cookie Policy_. Added categories: _Essential Cookies_, _Analytical Cookies_ and _Marketing Cookies_. Removed _Twitter_ and _Bing Ads_ as advertising vendors. Added cookie consent user settings. Other edits for readability and clarity.
* **2022/06/28:** added information about _iMazing Account_. Added _Auth0_ and _Google Cloud_ privacy policies.
* **2020/10/13:** added information about DigiDNA taking over license management. Organized data collection summary by type of service instead of partner. Clarified _Microsoft App Center_ data collection purposes. Added _Twitter_ and _Impact Radius_ to cookie policy.
* **2019/11/29:** added information regarding _Microsoft App Center_.
* **2018/05/23:** restructured the document, adding a detailed break down of partners and collected data.

12\. Contact
------------

If you have questions or wish to give us feedback on our current privacy policy, please [contact us.](https://imazing.com/contact) For further information concerning the use of our websites, please refer to our [Terms and Conditions.](https://imazing.com/terms-and-conditions)

Get news and offers right to **your inbox**.

Subscribe

Thank you for subscribing!

* * *

*  Features

*  Products

*  Get iMazing

*  Business

*  Support

*  Company

*  Legal
    
    * [Manage Cookies](javascript:void(0))

© DigiDNA SARL, 2008-2024. All rights reserved.  
iMazing ® is a registered trademark of DigiDNA SARL.

Available on **Mac & PC**

×

**iMazing** accesses your iPhone or iPad from your Mac or PC
------------------------------------------------------------

Please go to **[imazing.com](https://imazing.com/)** on your Mac or PC to download and install iMazing.

Type your email address to get a reminder and download link right to your inbox.

Send me a reminder

Please check your inbox, an email has been sent to  
.
